I feel sorry for you.
かわいそう
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
You're used to it, aren't you, camera?
慣れてるでしょ、カメラ?
Well, that's not the case at all.
え、全然そんなことない
lie?
嘘?
That's why we do such activities.
そういうことで、そういう活動してるもんね
Recently.
最近です
Hey, I'd like to ask you some questions.
ちょっとね、色々聞きたいんですよ
hey.
ね
How old are you now?
今、いくつなの?
I'm 19 years old.
19歳です
Where are you from?
出身は?
Akita prefecture.
秋田県です
Do you live here now?
今、こっちに住んでるの?
Yes, the situation has come up.
はい、状況してきて
Living alone?
一人暮らし?
yes.
はい
Or with your boyfriend?
それとも、彼、彼氏と?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏はいないです
Are you not there?
いないの?
Yeah.
うん
lie?
嘘?
Eh, what are you doing now, usually?
え、今何してるの、普段は?
I usually do some entertainment work.
普段は、ちょっと芸能のお仕事してます
Oh, hey, I heard a glimpse of it earlier.
あ、ちょっとね、さっきチラッと聞いちゃいましたけど
I came here from Akita and had a dream.
こ っち、秋田からこっち来て、夢がね、
There was just that.
あっただけ
I wanted to be an actress, so I joined an agency.
女優になりたくて、事務所入って、
But lately I've been getting gravure work.
でも、最近はグラビアのお仕事もらってて
What do you think of gravure?
グラビアって、どうですか?
I'm taking pictures in swimsuits and such.
なんか、水着とかで撮影してます
difficult.
難しい
Well, this is it, apart from the camera.
じゃあ、これね、カメラとか、別に
Because we're together.
一緒なんで
What kind of magazines do you publish?
結構、どういう雑誌とか出してるの?
picture?
え?
I don't really want to see it though.
全然見してくんないけど
I'm embarrassed.
恥ずかしくて
I want to see it.
見たいのよ
Hey, what are you appearing in?
へー、何に出てるかってことですか?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Don't tell me.
内緒ですよ
教えてくれるな
They said it was a secret.
内緒ですよっていうから
If you come within the main area.
要内でくると
Oh, is that so?
え、そうなの?
I think I'll buy some.
ちょっと買ってこようかな
Seriously, that's amazing.
マジで、すごいね
It's selling quite well, or rather, it's quite active.
結構売れてるというか、結構活動してるんだね
Oh, no, it's only been half a year ago.
え、全然、まだ半年前からですよ
Is that so?
そう なの?
Do you also work as an actress or something?
女優とかのような仕事もしてるの?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Is it fun or work?
楽しいですか、仕事も?
yes.
はい
Have you ever had a hard time?
辛いこととかはある?
Something painful...something painful or embarrassing.
辛いこと...辛いことか、恥ずかしいこと
Well, originally.
まあ、もともとね
I didn't come here just to do gravure.
今、グラビアやるぞって、こっち来たわけじゃないもんね
It's still a little bit, how long is it your first time?
まだちょっと、初めてどのくらいだ?
It's been half a year.
半年です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Is there still resistance?
まだ抵抗ある?
Not yet.
まだちょっと
I wanted to photograph every corner of Canada.
カナダの隅々まで、撮りたいなって思って
It's a hobby.
趣味でね
Is it your hobby?
趣味なんですか?
It's a hobby, right?
趣味でしょ
Oh, what are you doing?
お、何してんの?
Do you know?
知ってる?
That gravure thing.
そのグラビアって
People watching, what are you doing while watching?
見てる人、見ながらさ、何してるの?
Is it a video?
映像なんですか?
picture?
え?
Didn't know?
知らなかった?
It's so squishy.
プニプニだね
Not 20 people?
20人じゃなくて?
Can I get it for 200 people?
200人でもらって?
Will it increase from now on?
これから増えていくんだ?
Even from a parfait of clothes,
服のパフェからでも、
lol I like your face.
笑 顔がいいね
Isn't this what you do when you're filming?
撮影でこういうことするでしょ?
I won't.
しないですよ
What, you don't?
え、しないの?
I hear that a lot.
なんかよく聞くけど
Does that mean you'll be touched?
触られちゃうってことですか?
Doesn't the cameraman touch the director?
カメラマンに監督に触られたりしないの?
No.
ないです
Seriously?
マジで?
Well then, something special...
じゃあ、特別な...
Are you cutting it?
カットしてんの?
Does it smell very sweet?
すっごい甘い匂いする?
shampoo.
シャンプー
shampoo?
シャンプー?
When was the last time you slept?
最後ねってしたのいつ?
So in Akita, half a year ago.
秋田でだから、半年前
That's when I chewed it.
チューしたのもその時
I chewed it.
チューしちゃった
You looked a little like a woman for a moment.
今一瞬ちょっと女の顔になってたね
It's so cute.
すっげー可愛いね
It's really soft underneath.
めっちゃ下柔らかいね
Are there any soft spots?
柔らかいところあるんですか?
Below.
下の
That's sneaky.
ずるいね
I'd like to see it for a while.
ちょっともうさ、 見 たいんだけど
No, it's embarrassing.
いやー恥ずかしい
It's just a screw.
もう こんな、ほんのねじだから
ほんのねじだから
I'd like to see it.
見たいんだけど
This is the only underwear I wear anymore.
もうこの下着しかつけてない
Seriously?
マジで?
Are you not tired?
くすってないの?
this.
これ
I want to live here now.
ここにもう、ここに住みたい
Leave the residents here.
住民放置するからここに
Because I don't live there.
住まないから
You'll want to touch it on the way.
道方で触りたくなっちゃうよ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
She's fair-skinned, after all, Akita.
色白だね、やっぱ秋田
I'll smell it a little.
ちょっと匂い嗅ぐね
Oh no.
やべ
That's strange.
おかしいね
No way.
やだな
Oh no.
や だ
I can see the tantsu, though.
タンツ見えてるよ、でも
I'm wearing pants.
ズボンついてるな
I'm wearing pants though.
ズボンついてるけど
You'll want to take a closer look.
じっくり見たくなっちゃうね
It's too cute.
かわいすぎて
I see, this is what it looks like.
そっか、これは、 こんな感じだもんね
Well then, I guess I have no choice but to drink.
じゃあまあ、俺飲むしかないんだな
Oh, will you take a picture?
あ、撮ってくれるの?
Take, take, take.
撮って、撮って、撮って
The top opens, so you have a chance.
上が開くから、チャンス
Very long legs.
すっげぇ足長い
You never do poses like this, right?
こういうポーズは全然するでしょ?
But usually it's different with music.
でも普段はミュージックとか違えるから
We're together.
一緒じゃん
What's the difference?
何が違う?
I have a feeling.
なんか気持ちが
It's a feeling.
気持ちがね
This is completely private.
これはもう完全なプライベート
Could you please turn around for a moment?
ちょっと後ろ向いてごらん?
You've corrected your review a little bit now.
ちょっと今レビューに食い込みを直したでしょ
I'm super homeschooling.
超家教えしてる
That's terrible.
やばいね
I really like this.
すげぇ好きじゃん、これ
You like this too, right?
これも好きだろ?
Hey, kneel in front of me.
ちょっとさ、四つの前に膝つけて
Stick your butt out.
お尻突き出してごらん
Hey, okay.
ちょ、いいよ
It was something like this.
こういうもんであったね
Good conscience.
良心だな
It's so soothing.
めっちゃ癒やせにしてる
It's you.
お 前ね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look this way.
こっち向いてさ
It's usually a cycle.
普通にサイクルだな
Well then, can we do it?
じゃあさ、それでできちゃおうか
You don't need it anymore.
もういらないでしょ
It's the same as a swimsuit.
水着と一緒だよ
surely.
確かに
copper?
どう?
Did you touch me like this?
こうやって触られた?
It's just being photographed.
撮られるだけだもんね
I touch it myself.
自分で触ったりする
I thought about it for a while.
ちょっと考えたよ
Weren't you thinking about it just now?
ちょっと今考えてなかった?
I haven't thought about it.
考えてない
Are you going to touch it?
触るんでしょ?
I don't know.
分かんない
beautiful.
綺麗
It's so erotic.
めちゃくちゃエロいな
Isn't it so erotic?
めちゃくちゃエロくない?
That's terrible.
やばいね
Touch, touch.
触って触って
I guess it's okay to be patient.
我慢いいんだってかね
I haven't put it out yet.
まだ出したことない
Haven't you released it yet?
まだ出したことない?
In the world?
世の中に?
In front of the man you like?
好きな男の前ですか?
There have been two of us so far, haven't we?
今まで2人でしょ?
How was it?
どうだったんでしょ?
This is the fourth person.
これ4人目じゃん
It should be clean.
綺麗にすべき
Wow so beautiful.
うわーすっげー綺麗
Why do you hide it?
なんで隠すの?
Your face is cute.
顔可愛いな
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
There are some fans, right?
ファンの人とかいるわけでしょ?
It's getting sticky.
ベタベタになっちゃってるね
Will it become sticky?
ベタベタになる?
It became sticky.
ベタベタになっちゃった
delicious.
美味しい
I'm being licked.
舐められてる
It's insanely delicious.
めちゃくちゃ美味しい
You look really nice.
めっちゃいい顔するね
めっちゃいい顔する
You look really nice.
めっちゃいい顔するじゃん
I want to see this too.
こっちも見たい
You don't have this either.
こっちもないでしょ
Look behind the scenes.
裏見やって
Keep your legs wide open.
しっかり開いて足
You do poses like this, right?
こういうポーズもするでしょ
No way.
やだー
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗じゃん
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てくれ
This is the pose.
こう いうポーズだ
eye
め
It's so damn erotic.
ちゃ くちゃエロいね
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だね
Are you taking care of it?
お手入れしてるの?
Care?
お手入れ?
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
It's like being just born.
生まれたてみたいじゃん
She has a very erotic face.
めっちゃエロい顔してる
It's so naughty.
すごいやらしい
Hold my legs.
足抱えて
Open your legs properly.
足ちゃんと開いてね
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's so obscene.
す っごいやらしい
It's so naughty.
すっごいやらしい
Does this feel good?
こういう気持ちいいの?
Do you usually touch it yourself and do it like this?
普段自分で触って、 こんな感じにやってるの?
It's out now.
出てきたね、今ね
It's out.
出ちゃった
That's amazing.
すごいね
You have a great touch.
すっごい触り方するんだね
Are you going to do it now?
今するんですか?
It felt pretty good.
結構気持ちいいのにしたの
Can you do that?
そんなことできるの?
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
It's dangerous though.
やばいんだけど
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'm stopping it with my arm.
腕で止めてる
You stopped it with your arm.
腕で止めてたね
I stopped it.
止めちゃった
I put it on.
かけちゃった
It felt so good I could almost pull it out.
引くくらい気持ちよかったよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
You definitely did it recently, right?
絶対最近したでしょ?
Would you like me to say this?
こんなこと言ってもらう?
Didn't you make him a great person?
偉い人とかにしたでしょ?
A great person?
偉い人?
No, seriously.
いや、マジで
It was the best feeling ever.
今まで一番気持ちよかったんだけど
Is it true?
本当ですか?
An encounter like this, right?
こんな出会いでしょ?
Very full
めっちゃいっぱ
stomach.
い
Isn't it too good?
う ますぎない?
Were you drinking water?
水飲んでた?
Couldn't eat?
ご飯できなかった?
You're hiding it again.
また隠してんじゃん
This is also nice, like taking a bath together.
これもいいね、一緒にお風呂みたいな
Are you sure you haven't?
本当にしてない?
I haven't.
してないです
Do you do a lot of arrogance?
おなりばっかり?
It was in Akita, right?
秋田でしたでしょ?
boyfriend?
彼氏?
Tokyo is in that kind of entertainment world, right?
東京はそういう芸能界にいるわけでしょ?
There are such handsome people, right?
そういうイケメンの人とかいるでしょ?
You'll be invited, right?
誘われるでしょ?
No, that's not true.
いやいや、そんなことないです
Go back a little.
ちょっと 後ろに行ってさ
one
一
Did you do it twice?
回 はしたでしょ?
tomorrow!
あ、した!
Did you applaud?
拍手をした?
Did you do it once?
一回したの?
Did you only do it once?
一回だけしたの?
I can't see it.
見えないです
Why is that?
なんでそれは?
Because he's an invisible person.
見えない人だから
What is that?
それは何?
Impossible?
無理?
Let's ask later, then.
後で聞こう、じゃあ
Hey, you two go.
ちょっとさ、二人行って
Bowlers did this too.
ボーラーもこんなのしてた
That's dangerous.
やばいよね
It's dangerous though.
やばいんだけど
Have you ever done something like this?
こんなのしたことある?
Just once.
一回でさ
Because I'm pinching it and moving it like this.
挟んで、こうやって動かしてるから
Have you never done it?
や ったことない?
do not have.
ない
Do you know what this is called?
これ何て言うか知ってる?
I know.
知ってる
Do you know?
知ってるの?
What do you say?
何て言うの?
Titty fuck.
パイズリ
How do you know?
なんで知ってるの?
I know your name.
名前は知ってる
Isn't that what you're telling the hire person?
ハイヤーさんに教えてることだろ?
different.
違う
Umemiya Tatsuo?
梅みやタツオ?
Was it wrong?
違った?
Are you talking slimy?
ヌルヌル言ってる?
Slimy.
ヌルヌル
Sorry, I can't either.
ごめんなさい、私もダメです
How do you do that?
どうやってさ、するの?
everytime.
いつも
Is that so?
そうあるの?
usually.
普通
usually?
普通?
I don't know what's normal though.
普通がわかんないんだけど
I can only remove it.
外しかされない
Do you mean outside?
外って言うの?
what?
何?
That's how you do it.
そうやってやるんだ
You're shouting.
声出しちゃってるじゃん
Hey, I just brought it out, but...
ちょっと、 もうね、さっき出しちゃったけど、
I can't show my face.
顔できないですよ
Does it feel good when you touch it yourself?
自分で触ると気持ちいいの?
Hmm.
うーん
But it feels better to touch it than it does to me.
でも自分より触れた方が気持ちいい
What, you mean it felt better when you touched me earlier?
え、さっき触られた方が 気持ちよかったってこと?
Wouldn't it feel better?
もっと気持ちいいんじゃない?
Just come out.
ちょっと、出たら
copper?
どう?
Good.
よいしょ
Okay, do this.
よし、これやってね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hey.
ねえ
That's amazing.
すっごいじゃん
Good.
よいしょ
Has it been a while?
久々なの?
It's been a while, though.
久々じゃないのか、でも
Long time no see.
久々
Has it been a while?
久々なの?
amazing.
すごい
Look here.
こっち、見て
Erotic.
エロい
That's a nice butt.
良いお尻だね
That's a really beautiful mango.
すっごい綺麗なマンゴーだね
What should I do?
どうしよう?
Dangerous, dangerous.
あぶない、あぶない
Wear it on your shoulders.
肩ペタってつけてさ
I can see your butthole too.
お尻の穴も見えるよ
Banh mi.
バンミー
I'm messing with my own hands.
自分の手動いちゃってるね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Look behind me.
後ろに手ついてごらん
Please come out and give it to me.
出てみましてあげてごらん
Take it slow.
ゆっくりさ
Take it out slowly.
ゆっくり出して
yes.
そう
appear?
見える?
Oh no, I put it out.
やばい、出した
good?
いい?
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Inside.
中に
good?
いい?
Take it inside.
中に出して
Why don't you go?
行ってごらん?
That's good.
いいのね
Did you wake up a little?
ちょっと起き上がったかな?
Open your legs.
足開いて
A lot came out.
いっぱい出ちゃったね